jobsindubai.com 2019-09-26

# Jobs in Dubai

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the Jobs In Dubai . Com INC. (JID) website at JobsInDubai.Com INC. The website is owned by Jobs In Dubai . Com , company registered in Ontario, Canada **Tel:** +1 (818) 661-6374 [Mon - Fri] , Email : Privacy.Terms@jobsindubai.com

At JID your privacy is of paramount importance. As the custodians of your personal information, we have developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is always protected while you are using the JID website.

By accessing or using the website, you agree to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this website.

**Note to minors**  
We do not knowingly market to or encourage children, minors or anyone under the age of 18 to use our services and we request that children do not submit information to us.

**About JID and the information we collect**  
JID operates a professional networking / jobs portal, offering users a set of tools to connect to a global community network of job seekers. JID is party paid and also free service to all members that meet our age criteria, please read our Terms of use for more information.

When you enter JID, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all JID users. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to JID. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

In our online registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your name, your email address, your gender, and your date of birth, your location details and some optional details about yourself. These details are available to you anytime, and are capable of being corrected, altered or updated through your "Profile" page.

At your own discretion, you may choose to post additional facts about yourself. These facts may include sensitive personal data such as your ethnic origin, level of education, professional qualifications. You may choose to volunteer sensitive personal data to us when you create your profile. Photographs and content on your resume SnapShot may reveal sensitive personal data about you and we strictly forbid any mentions of your personal information such as your contact telephone number, or your home address on any of our sections that are directly related to our social networking service called "Connect". The exceptions may be your resume; you may chose to have all information relevant for prospective employers to view and use only for the purpose of hiring you. 

We internally use personal information of our users to statistically analyze site usage, to comply with applicable law, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We may also use personal information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. We believe these uses allow us to improve our website and to tailor your online experience to better meet your needs. We use personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our" Products and Services Available On The Site" link.

You may wish to receive emails from us in respect to new message notifications, or for other purposes related to the use of the website. You can opt in or out from these messages via your "Personal Settings" page.

Your profile data will be available to other users of the website if you select the "Enable Public Profile" in your access setting.

By registering on the website you acknowledge and agree that the profile data and other postings that you provide, including sensitive personal data, may be accessed from countries outside of Canada. Please note that countries outside of Canada may have lower standards of data protection laws.

By registering on one of our partner websites, you will be providing personal information to our partner. Their privacy policies and practices are separate to those of JID and we strongly encourage you to familiarize yourself with the policies and practices displayed on the partners website.

**Disclosure of your information**  
We do not sell or rent out any personal information about you to any third party. We do disclose information in aggregate for marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password and address is not disclosed at all.

In order to maintain a healthy community, JID would cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law if we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served.

Your use of other users' information

You may not use other users' information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of those who misuse other users' information or who otherwise violates the Terms of use.

**Inactivity**  
You may choose to leave your account dormant for an unlimited period of time.

**Control of your password**  
You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. This can be done via your personal if you click on your "My Account" link.

**Reviewing and changing your personal information**  
Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your personal information including:

Your contact email address;  
Your profile, photographs;  
Your city, region, and country of residence;  
Your password.   
Promptly update your information if it changes by signing in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information.

We welcome any comments or queries you may have, so please feel free to send a message to our Customer Service Dept for the purposes of altering your information or changing your settings.

**Security**  
JID has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. JID uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information by hosting VeriSign's Secure Socket Layer. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at JID work hard to ensure your secure use of our site.

**Deleting your Profile**  
The Administrator of the JID network has the following right to delete your profile from the JID database if the user is reported and found to be using unacceptable language, is a menace to other users, uses or displays material online that is offensive to social and religious sensitivities to a region.

**Invite a Friend**  
If a user decides to use our Invitation option to invite a friend to our website, users have an option to add their friend's email addresses. JID will automatically send their friend an email inviting them to join JID's website. JID stores this email address for the purpose of automatically associating the friend with the user sending the invitation. JID does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. The friend may contact JID to request the removal of this information from our database.

By providing us with information about a friend, you confirm their informed consent to do so.

**Uploading your Contacts**  
If a user decides to upload their contacts, email invitations will be sent on the user behalf to everyone on their address book, JID will not store your passwords. JID will only stores the name and email address of the contacts for the purpose of automatically associating the friend with the user sending the invitation. JID does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and future notifications.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy or email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, disclose it.

**What information do we collect?**

  * We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as email, or participate in another site feature.
  * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
  * We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
  * Like many websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  

  * To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the “How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?” section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and ‘members-only’ content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

**How do we protect visitor information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above. 

**Do we use "cookies"?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Chrome, Safari, Firefox) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service. 

**Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term “outside parties” does not include Jobs In Dubai .Com INC . It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?**  
To modify your online account information, sign into the "My Account" section of our site. 

To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the “My Account” section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production. Please <https://jobsindubai.com/contact.asp> to remove information. 

**Third party links**  
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work). 

**Age of Consent**  
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site. 

**Changes to our policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on Jan 18, 2016. 

**Questions and feedback**  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at customercare@jobsindubai.com 

**Online Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
